ALEKSANDR ANDREYKO

Frontend Developer

+374 (98) 990665 # www.linkedin.com/in/chgrin/ # marphalina@gmail.com # telegram: @chgrin

Commercial experience: over 4 years. For the last 3 years I was working as the only frontend developer in the team, which taught me to understand the areas of responsibility and set fair assessments of tasks.

SKILLS



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer I National Media Group, Moscow, Russia December 2020 - November 2023

Support and development of new functionality for the channel sites of CTC Media holding (**domashniy.ru**, **chetv.ru**, **ctclove.ru**) and some third-party projects, for example, the website of a film project pitching contest **pitchlab.ctcmedia.ru**. Refactoring and getting rid of legacy on projects.

Implemented tasks of different levels:

- user authorization
- adding a subscription to view content without ads
- complete redesign of the site
- participation in the migration of projects to another backend framework
- splitting site elements into independent widgets and optimizing their loading

The stack is used on the projects: javascript + react + redux + a bit jquery + stylus/sass.

Jr Frontend Developer I Leomax, Moscow, Russia August 2019 - December 2020

Development of a landing page for the company's products on React. Support and creation of new sections in current online shops (jquery + yii) and (jquery + bitrix).

EDUCATION

Programming algorithms | Yandex Contest | 2023 - Present

Sorting algorithms

Frontend | Self-Education | 2020 - Present

React, Redux, Webpack, Typescript

Frontend Developer I GeekBrains, Online I 2020

HTML, CSS, React

Frontend Developer I HTMLAcademy, Online I 2019

HTML, CSS, JavaScript

Advertising and Multimedia Technology Specialist

The First Moscow Educational Complex | Moscow, Russia | 09.2012 - 07.2016

Advertising, marketing and technology tools for creation of advertisement products

CERTIFICATIONS

- GeekBrains «HTML&CSS» https://gb.ru/certificates/701170.en
- GeekBrains «ReactJS» https://gb.ru/certificates/863760.en